# **EZEUGWU IFEANYI CHRISTIAN**

State of Origin:Enugu StateL. G. A:UdenuSex:Male

Date of Birth: June 1, 1995

Place of Birth: Onitsha, Anambra state.

Marital Status: Single

### CONTACTS

**1** 07069200690

ifeanyiezeugwu0@gmail.com

Q Nigeria

### SKILLS

- Human resource management skill
- Team player/delegation skill
- Problem-Solving
- Computer Literacy
- · Conflict resolution management
- Time management skill
- Adaptability

### HOBBIES

- Reading
- Music
- Blockchain
- Cooking

## EDUCATION

#### PRIMARY, SECONDARY SCHOOL

Mater christi school, onitsha.

2001 - 2007,

2007 - 2013

#### TERTIARY INSTITUTION

university of uyo

2015 - 2019

### REFEREES

Engr. Marcus Ugwuanyi 08035924462

Mrs. Eno-Ubong B. Usungurua 08038786959

Sir. Able Tola Newton 08032624838

### PROFILE

I am a political scientist, public administrator, public policy analyst, data analyst with over 2 years of experience in company management and administration, strong creative and analytical skills, team player with an eye for detail.

### EXPERIENCE

#### **REGIONAL MANAGER**

#### **Betking Betting Company**

#### 2020 - 2021

- Managed over 3 branches in Uyo, Akwa Ibom state
- · In-charge of staff recruitment
- Delegation of responsibilities to workers
- Creating quality and conducive environment for customers and staff

#### NATIONAL YOUTH SERVICE CORPS, AKWA IBOM STATE.

Social studies, Civic Education and Government teacher.

#### 2021 - 2022

- Planning and compiling of lecture notes and materials.
- Creating a quality and good teacher-student relationship.
- Preparation of assessment, text, quiz, examination.
- Getting the students actively involved in social and educational activities, like inter-house sports, state schools sports competition, state schools spelling competition, local government schools challenge cup.

### CERTIFICATES/AWARDS

- Testimonial (mater Christi school, Onitsha)
- SSCE/WAEC (mater Christi school, Onitsha)
- B.Sc. Political Science and Public Administration (university of uyo)
- Certificate of one-year completion of National Service (NYSC)
- Award of Hard work and dedication (secondary commercial school, Ibesikpo Asuntan, Akwa Ibom state)
- Certificate of completion of data analysis (Entry Level Academy)